greatnonprofits.org 2010-06-12

# Our Privacy Policy | GreatNonprofits: Find non-profits and charities to review, donate, or volunteer.

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. Our ongoing commitment to the protection of your privacy is essential to maintaining the relationship of trust that exists between GreatNonprofits and all of our users, whether they be nonprofit organizations, volunteers, clients or donors of nonprofits, or other visitors to the site. This notice of our privacy policy is intended to help you understand our online information security practices.

### The Information We Collect

You may have accessed GreatNonprofits directly by visiting our Web site, the home page of which is located at www.GreatNonprofits.org, or through the Web site of one of our third-party partners. This notice applies to all information you submit to GreatNonprofits, whether through the GreatNonprofits Web site or through the Web site of one of our Partners. Please note that we cannot be responsible for the information you submit directly to third parties, including our Partners, who may have their own posted policies regarding the collection and use of your information. We urge you to review the policies of our Partners through whom you may access our services.

GreatNonprofits collects user submitted account information such as your email address to identify you and send you notifications related to the use of the service. GreatNonprofits also collects user submitted location information such as city, state, or zip code. GreatNonprofits also collects user submitted photos, reviews, and ratings of nonprofits.

Some information collected is not explicitly submitted by the user; we log your browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp.

### How We Use Information

Your full name and email address may also be used when you send an email notification to a friend (such as in an invitation, or when sharing a review). We may also use your email address to send you updates or news regarding our site, but you may choose not to receive email of this type by accessing the “Account” tab of the web site and updating your notification settings. Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message).

Browser-type related information, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp data help us diagnose problems with our server, administer GreatNonprofits, and otherwise provide the highest possible level of service to you. In addition, we use this information to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the site and to inform advertisers of such information as well as the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, their advertising banners.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We do not, however, sell, rent or trade our volunteer, administrator, nonprofit, or general newsletter email addresses to outside parties.

Please be aware that, to the extent required to provide our services, we share your Information with volunteers, nonprofit organizations, or our Partners, as applicable:

### For Newsletter Subscribers

We may use our email lists for sending out our newsletter and other GreatNonprofits outbound communications, such as product enhancements, tool upgrades, or membership news.

Additionally, for volunteers with a personal account who have accessed GreatNonprofits through www.greatnonprofits.org or a Partner’s Web site: If you indicate to us that you are interested in creating a personalized account, the information we gather from you will be used to permit you to: access the account, customize outbound email services, review your referral history and/or post a resume that can be sent as an attachment to inquiries you make using the GreatNonprofits service.

### For Nonprofit Organizations

If you submit Information to us as a nonprofit organization, then, subject to the terms and conditions as a nonprofit member of GreatNonprofits, your Information (excluding your EIN number) will be accessible by anyone who accesses GreatNonprofits. In addition, we may share your Information, including your EIN number, with selected Partners in order to verify your organization’s identity and tax status.

### Children’s Privacy

We welcome users of all ages, including children under the age of thirteen. Due to our status as a non-profit organization, we are not required to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). However, we strongly encourage our users aged thirteen and under to use our services only with parental consent.

### Cookies

Cookies are tiny data files that Web sites commonly write to your hard drive when you visit them so that they can remember you when you visit. A cookie file contains information that can identify you anonymously and maintain your account’s privacy. Our site uses cookies to maintain a user’s identity between sessions so that the site can be personalized based on user preferences or a user’s history. You can set your Web browser to prompt you before you accept a cookie, accept cookies automatically or reject all cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies from this Web site, then you may not be able to access and use all or part of this Web site or benefit from the information and services which it offers.

### Third-party Access and Use

Occasionally, we or our Partners hire third-party service providers to help provide or improve the services we offer you. Sometimes it is necessary for these providers to have access to the Information we collect about you. In those cases, we take reasonable steps to ensure that these providers do not use or otherwise disclose any Information we collect about you except for the purpose of fulfilling their service obligations to us and our Partners.

In the unlikely event that GreatNonprofits undergoes a sale or transfer of all or substantially all of its assets, the acquiring entity will be subject to this Privacy Policy in its use of your personally identifiable Information. In addition, in the further unlikely event that GreatNonprofits is adjudicated bankrupt or insolvent (a) there will be no further use or disclosure of your personally identifiable Information by GreatNonprofits and (b) your personally identifiable Information will be destroyed. In addition, there will be no use or disclosure of your personally identifiable Information by any entity that acquires assets of GreatNonprofits pursuant to such bankruptcy or insolvency proceedings.

Your privacy is very important to us. Due to factors beyond our control, however, we cannot fully ensure that your Information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be legally obligated to disclose Information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access your Personal Information.

### Links

This site contains links to other sites. GreatNonprofits is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

### How You Can Review Or Correct Your Information

If you are a nonprofit member or user with an account (either through www.GreatNonprofits.org or a Partner’s Web site) you can modify your personal information at any time by accessing the “Account” section of the site

You do not need to contact us to access your record or to make any changes. If you have problems changing your Information, please contact Community Services at support@greatnonprofits.org.

### For Nonprofit Organizations

If you are a nonprofit administrator, you may modify your organizational information at any time by accessing the “Account” section of the site. You do not need to contact us to access your record or to make any changes. If you have problems changing your organization’s Information, please contact Community Services at support@greatnonprofits.org

If you are a nonprofit member or volunteer with an account and would like to have your Information deleted from the site, you may do so by contacting Community Services at support@greatnonprofits.org

### Your Ability to Opt-out of Newsletters & Communications

Subscriptions to GreatNonprofits newsletters are optional and GreatNonprofits allows nonprofit organizations, volunteers, subscribers or other users to unsubscribe from newsletters at any time. In each newsletter we provide instructions regarding how to opt-out from receiving future newsletter mailings. You can also email us at support@greatnonprofits.org to remove your name from our newsletter subscription data base and ensure that you will cease receiving future newsletters from us.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the GreatNonprofits service, such as the occasional service and product announcement or administrative message, that are considered part of your GreatNonprofits account without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of Information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Information we collect online.

### Changes to Policy

You should visit this page periodically to review any changes to the Privacy Policy. Continued use of the GreatNonprofits Web site following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

### How To Contact Us

We appreciate your questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with GreatNonprofits. Please send email to support@greatnonprofits.org or you can send snail mail to 695 Arkansas St., San Francisco, CA 94107.

Effective Date: March 30, 2007
